<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Canadian Cities</string>
    <string name="initial">Pick a city!</string>
    <string-array name="cities">
        <item>Calgary</item>
        <item>Victoria</item>
        <item>Vancouver</item>
        <item>Toronto</item>
        <item>Lethbridge</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="info">
        <item>Calgary is the largest city in the western Canadian province of Alberta and the largest metro area of the three Prairie Provinces. As of 2021, the city proper had a population of 1,306,784 and a metropolitan population of 1,481,806, making it the third-largest city and fifth-largest metropolitan area in Canada. Calgary\'s economy includes activity in the energy, financial services, film and television, transportation and logistics, technology, manufacturing, aerospace, health and wellness, retail, and tourism sectors. The Calgary Metropolitan Region is home to Canada\'s second-highest number of corporate head offices among the country\'s 800 largest corporations. In 2015, Calgary had the highest number of millionaires per capita of any major Canadian city. </item>
        <item>Victoria is the capital city of the Canadian province of British Columbia, on the southern tip of Vancouver Island off Canada\'s Pacific coast. The city has a population of 91,867, and the Greater Victoria area has a population of 397,237. The city of Victoria is the 7th most densely populated city in Canada with 4,405.8 inhabitants per square kilometre (11,411/sq mi). Victoria is the southernmost major city in Western Canada and is about 100 km (62 mi) southwest from British Columbia\'s largest city of Vancouver on the mainland. The city is about 100 km (62 mi) from Seattle by airplane, seaplane, ferry, or the Victoria Clipper passenger-only ferry, and 40 km (25 mi) from Port Angeles, Washington, by ferry Coho across the Strait of Juan de Fuca.  </item>
        <item>Vancouver is a major city in western Canada, located in the Lower Mainland region of British Columbia. As the most populous city in the province, the 2021 census recorded 662,248 people in the city, up from 631,486 in 2016. The Greater Vancouver area had a population of 2.6 million in 2021, making it the third-largest metropolitan area in Canada. Vancouver has the highest population density in Canada, with over 5,700 people per square kilometre. Vancouver is one of the most ethnically and linguistically diverse cities in Canada: 46 percent of its residents are not native English speakers, 44 percent are native speakers of neither English nor French, and 51.6 percent of residents belong to visible minority groups.</item>
        <item>Toronto is the capital city of the Canadian province of Ontario. With a recorded population of 2,794,356 in 2021, it is the most populous city in Canada and the fourth most populous city in North America. The city is the anchor of the Golden Horseshoe, an urban agglomeration of 9,765,188 people (as of 2021) surrounding the western end of Lake Ontario, while the Greater Toronto Area proper had a 2021 population of 6,712,341. Toronto is an international centre of business, finance, arts, sports and culture, and is recognized as one of the most multicultural and cosmopolitan cities in the world.</item>
        <item>Lethbridge is a city in the province of Alberta, Canada. With a population of 101,482 in its 2019 municipal census, Lethbridge became the fourth Alberta city to surpass 100,000 people. The nearby Canadian Rocky Mountains contribute to the city\'s warm summers, mild winters, and windy climate. Lethbridge lies southeast of Calgary on the Oldman River. Lethbridge is the commercial, financial, transportation and industrial centre of southern Alberta. The city\'s economy developed from drift mining for coal in the late 19th century and agriculture in the early 20th century. Half of the workforce is employed in the health, education, retail and hospitality sectors, and the top five employers are government-based.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>